

SWATI SATPATHY

House No – SB/73, Aaditya Enclave, Kanan Vihar, Phase- II, Patia. Bhubaneswar-751024. Odisha.

Mobile:9348349409,9776911873 E.mail: satpathyswati84@gmail.com

VISION

To increase the shareholder value and maximize profit by improving the operational efficiencies and maximum utilization for the available resources.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To find a challenging position to meet my competencies, capabilities, skills, education and experience. To achieve business excellence and ambitious growth plan to excel professionally by utilizing extremely passionate and enthusiastic, predictable expertise, with purpose to be in a leading organization with grow & giving philosophy.

KEYS FOR SUCCESS

- Integrity
- Ethics
- Leadership
- Team Work
- Training
- rship Recognition
- Communication
- Continuous Improvement
- Accuracy & Transparency

KEY STRENGTH

I strongly believe in Positive attitude & self interest. These two attributes can sell anything in this world if we have a passion for it. In my philosophy, we must adopt all methods of selling except those which harms anybody's interest or violates the standard norms of the company or constituency. Apart from these I have lot of confidence to meet the target because of the following:

- High level computer skills including Excel, Word and PowerPoint.
- Handling back office work efficiently and effectively.
- Strong business development capabilities with motivational team work.
- Being adaptable and flexible to changing work place.
- Active toastmasters' public speaker.

.

CAREER HISTORY

Oct 2019- till present Business Development Executive

Hexagen Technologies Pvt Limited

Key Responsibilities

- Cold calling to arrange meetings with potential customers for new business.
- Conduct Market Research and analysis to create marketing initiatives for promoting the services.
- Coordinating with Lead Generation team for positive prospects and delivering proposal within timeline to interested clients.
- Build a sales pipeline by cultivating prospects, creating new business opportunities and managing existing customer relationships using CRM tools.
- Sending follow up mails and calls to the clients.
- Responding to incoming emails and phone enquiries.
- Negotiating on price, cost, delivery and specifications with Specific Departments and convey the same to clients.
- Maintaining quality service by establishing and enforcing organization standards.

Aug 2018-May 2019 Team Leader Operations

SMA e-Expert Pvt Limited

Key Responsibilities

- Analysis of All component progress report on daily basis and work on single check pending cases.
- Delegating tasks to team members and set target for Closure report day wise.
- Take necessary action to complete the in TAT and Out TAT cases.
- Send intimation mail for delay in service when cases pending from external end.
- Analyzing case received and completed in a day and prepares daily productivity report.
- Making QC calls to the client for the feedback.
- Interact with different clients regarding case matter and the services provided by the company as and when required.
- Prepared Performance review report of both team members and case status for monthly review meeting.
- Make single check pending cases and work on the target.
- Focus on quality work at the same time maintains TAT.
- Provide Training to new joiners on all aspects of verification.

- Ensure delivery of reports with excellence and meeting timelines and committed quality levels at the same time.
- Prepared completed cases Annexure report and send to Client for Billing.
- SPOC for all case handling.
- Convince client for clear insufficiency raised at the time of case approval.
- Addressing clients concerns and complaints.

Dec 2017-Jun2018 Commercial Executive

Riverside Utilities Pvt Ltd

Key Responsibilities

- Prepare daily MIS of collections Division wise and sent to CESU.
- Make monthly Analysis of BU performance Target vs. Achieved.
- Prepared Incentive structure, Fooding bill and fuel expenses of Field staff.
- Coordinate with field staff for collection report on daily basis.
- Make Analysis of payment trend, paid& unpaid consumer report.
- Bill correction and revision of Consumers.
- Studied Analysis wings cases, follow up with concerned Department and make status report of the closed cases.
- Manage and ensure that all meetings are timely arranged.
- Provide collections analysis report to the Business Units to support in enhancing arrear collections.
- Undertake any other duties as per assigned.

May 2016-Dec 2017 MIS Executive

IACM Smart Learn Ltd

Key Responsibilities

- Preparing reports & Data base of all centers for both HO and Center levels.
- Upload Trainees Offer Letter and Salary Slip in NSDC portal.
- Documentation processing for event management at centers.
- Tracking rentention Report of Trainees.
- Perform Data Analysis for generating reports on periodic basis.
- Creating MIS report and presenting it to the Concerned Department.
- Documentation of events performed in placement Division.
- Follow-up with Team members for weekly and monthly target.
- Making post Tracker feed Back from Trainees at different centers.

October 2013 - May 2016 Business Associate

TATA AIA Life Insurance Company ltd

Key Responsibilities

- Recruitment of Advisors and indirect team through Business Associates.
- To manage them and ensure that they achieve their targets, and in turn achieve organizational goals.
- Joint field work with advisors, mentoring skills finance and insurance industry awareness.
- Target sets for each advisors and the indirect team.
- Make sure every advisor should activate in each month and Goal Sheet achievement.
- Maintain Data base of potential customers of each advisor and assist team accordingly.

August 2008 – July 2009 Relationship Manager

M/s Sadhaba Marine Pvt. Ltd.

Key Responsibilities

- Collect database relating to product based client from state, national and abroad as well to fix an appointment for detailing the product specifications & exceptions.
- Identify New Clients and generate sales volume.
- Recovery of Old Debts from Clients.
- Visited Client site for reconciliation of Debtor accounts as and when required.
- Looking after the HR section and Manage petty Cash.
- Maintaining petty cash ledger Book.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

- **2008:** Master in Business Administration (MBA) under Utkal University, Bhubaneswar in the year 2008 with accreditation of First class Distinction.
- **2005:** Bachelor in Commerce (B.Com) under North Orissa University, Baripada in the year 2005 with accreditation of First class Distinction.
- **2002:** Intermediate in Science (I.Sc) under Council of Higher Secondary Education, Orissa in the year 2002 with Second class accreditation.
- **1999:** Matriculation under Board of Secondary Education, Orissa in the year 1999 with First class accreditation.
 - ➤ Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Application (PGDCA) from Xavier Board for Computer Applications in the year 2008 with accreditation of A+Grade.
 - > Six months Summer Internship Training at Nokia Retail center, Bhubaneswar under Nokia's Global Graduate Development Program in the year 2008.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name : Jogendranath Satpathy

Mother's Maiden Name : Bharati Panigrahi
Date of Birth : 9th March 1984

Nationality : Indian
Religion : Hindu
Sex : Female
Marital Status : Married

Dancing, singing, Acting, learn new languages,

Hobbies & Interest : Travelling with family and friends.

Odia, English, Hindi, Bengali & Conversational

Language Fluency : French

DECLARATION

I, hereby declare that the above furnished data is true, correct and accurate to the best of knowledge & belief.

Bhubaneswar

Dated 11.02.2020

SWATI SATPATHY